Andrew Perniciaro

SAINT PETERSBURG, FL (609) 214-6319 ANDREW.PERNICIARO@GMAIL.COM

Professional Links

GitHub

https://github.com/aperniciaro

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aperniciaro01/

Portfolio

https://portfolio...

Professional Summary

A broad background in web development, research and analysis, and enterprise strategy across different sectors and industries. Brings value in the technical, vision, and personal facets of organizations in the public- and private-sectors; local, regional, or global. A quick learner, self-starter, and team leader, comfortable working across business lines, functional areas, and with stakeholders internal or external.

Skills

C#/.NET
SQL
Javascript/React
HTML/CSS
Legal Research
Quantitative and Qualitative Research
Microsoft Office Suite
Enterprise Architecture
Report Writing and Analysis

Full Stack Web Development

Projects

Armchair GM: Web-based baseball general manager simulation, using Javascript/React and C#/.NET

Minesweeper: Web-based reproduction of classic game using HTML/CSS and Javascript

Treasury Financial Manual: Requirements gathering and project oversight for Adobe CQ-based regulations publishing application

Civil Conflict Outcomes and Recurrence: 90+ page undergraduate thesis on comparative views of conflict theory using historical data and case studies

Work Experience

CONFLICTS ANALYST

White & Case, LLP 2017 - 2018

- · Analyzed incoming business for conflicts of interest firm-wide
- · Coordinated compliance cases across business lines and global practice locations
- Provided "know-your-customer" research on diverse companies, institutions, and executives

RISK ANALYST II

BB&T Co.

2014 - 2016

- Provided research and analysis on prospective large dollar commercial and personal loan borrowers
- Queried and synthesized data from a variety of legal and public records databases
- · Performed quality control analyses on previous research and business processes

FINANCIAL PROGRAM SPECIALIST

US Treasury Department 2009 - 2013

- Worked across business units to develop and improve business architecture and operational processes
- Developed a Bureau-wide data schema, and specifications for a web-based regulations management system
- Co-led a workgroup on selection and oversight of financial agents
- Authored and edited data-analysis, research, position documents, and dashboards used by senior management
- Combined Federal Campaign keyworker, 2011
- · Employee of the Month, March 2010

Education

SUNCOAST DEVELOPERS GUILD

2019

- Built proficiency in HTML, CSS, Javascript/React, SQL, and C#/.NET in an immersive, full-time program, full stack web development program
- · Created front- and back-ends of webpages using bleeding-edge coding tools
- Created a capstone project simulating major-league baseball roster building

NEW COLLEGE OF FLORIDA

2004 - 2008

BA - Political Science/International & Area Studies

- New College is the public honors college of Florida, using a non-traditional academic system focused on self-motivated learning and research
- Completed coursework including international and domestic politics, history, micro- and macro-economics, philosophy, and sociology
- Elected member of the Student Academic Council and International Studies Committee, 2007-2008